export let level_info = [

    {
        'id': 1,
        'type': 'Vocab',
        'english':['I','am/is/are','you','cool','pretty','book','have','car','this','that'],
        'japanese':['わたし','は~です','あなた','かっこいい','きれい','ほん','が~あります','くるま','これ','それ'],
        'japanese_sent':['わたし は さら です','わたし は さら です','あなた は とむ です','わたし は かっこいい です','あなた は きれい です','わたし は ほん が あります','あなた は くるま が あります','これ は ほん です','それ は くるま です','ほん です'],
        'words': [
            {
                'japanese':'わたし',
                'english':'I',
                'romanji':'watashi',
                'example_japanese':'わたし は さら です.',
                'example_romanji':'watashi wa sara desu.',
                'example_english':'I am Sara.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'は~です',
                'english':'am/is/are',
                'romanji':'wa~desu',
                'example_japanese':'わたし は さら です.',
                'example_romanji':'watashi wa sara desu.',
                'example_english':'I am Sara.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'あなた',
                'english':'you',
                'romanji':'anata',
                'example_japanese':'あなた は とむ です.',
                'example_romanji':'anata wa tomu desu.',
                'example_english':'You are Tom.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'かっこいい',
                'english':'cool',
                'romanji':'kakkoii',
                'example_japanese':'わたし は かっこいい です.',
                'example_romanji':'watashi wa kakkoii desu.',
                'example_english':'I am cool.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'きれい',
                'english':'pretty',
                'romanji':'kirei',
                'example_japanese':'あなた は きれい です.',
                'example_romanji':'anata wa kirei desu.',
                'example_english':'You are pretty.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'ほん',
                'english':'book',
                'romanji':'hon',
                'example_japanese':'ほん です.',
                'example_romanji':'hon desu.',
                'example_english':'It is a book.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'が~あります',
                'english':'have',
                'romanji':'ga~arimasu',
                'example_japanese':'わたし は ほん が あります.',
                'example_romanji':'watashi wa hon ga arimasu.',
                'example_english':'I have a book.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'くるま',
                'english':'car',
                'romanji':'kuruma',
                'example_japanese':'あなた は くるま が あります.',
                'example_romanji':'anata wa kuruma ga arumasu.',
                'example_english':'You have a car.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'これ',
                'english':'this',
                'romanji':'kore',
                'example_japanese':'これ は ほん です.',
                'example_romanji':'kore wa book desu.',
                'example_english':'This is a book.',
                'seen':'false'
            },
            {
                'japanese':'それ',
                'english':'that',
                'romanji':'sore',
                'example_japanese':'それ は くるま です.',
                'example_romanji':'sore wa car desu.',
                'example_english':'That is a car.',
                'seen':'false'
            }
        ],
        'questions': [
            {
                'question':'I',
                'answer':'わたし',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'am/is/are',
                'answer':'は~です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'You',
                'answer':'あなた',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'わたし',
                'answer':'I',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'は~です',
                'answer':'am/is/are',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'あなた',
                'answer':'you',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'Cool',
                'answer':'かっこいい',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Pretty',
                'answer':'きれい',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Book',
                'answer':'ほん',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Have',
                'answer':'が~あります',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Car',
                'answer':'くるま',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'This',
                'answer':'これ',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'かっこいい',
                'answer':'cool',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'きれい',
                'answer':'pretty',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'ほん',
                'answer':'book',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'が~あります',
                'answer':'have',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'くるま',
                'answer':'car',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'これ',
                'answer':'this',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'それ',
                'answer':'that',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'true'
            },
            {
                'question':'That',
                'answer':'それ',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            
        ],
        'tower': [
            {
                'question':'That',
                'answer':'それ',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Have',
                'answer':'が~あります',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'am/is/are',
                'answer':'は~です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'I',
                'answer':'わたし',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'You',
                'answer':'あなた',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Cool',
                'answer':'かっこいい',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Pretty',
                'answer':'きれい',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Book',
                'answer':'ほん',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'Car',
                'answer':'くるま',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'This',
                'answer':'これ',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'You have a car',
                'answer':'あなた は くるま が あります',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'This is a book',
                'answer':'これ は ほん です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'I am Sara',
                'answer':'わたし は さら です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'That is a car',
                'answer':'それ は くるま です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'I have a book',
                'answer':'わたし は ほん が あります',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'You are pretty',
                'answer':'あなた は きれい です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'It is a book',
                'answer':'ほん です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'I am cool',
                'answer':'わたし は かっこいい です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'You are Tom',
                'answer':'あなた は とむ です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            {
                'question':'I am Sara',
                'answer':'わたし は さら です',
                'seen':'false',
                'correct': 0,
                'japanese': 'false'
            },
            
        ]
    }



]